Office of the Dean of Arts and Sciences Records UA195
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Faculty Information Sheets, 1990 -- 2008; UA195.005; 5.35 Linear Feet
  - Classics, 1999 -- 2003; UA195.005.005.00020 (Box 5)
  - Computer Science, 1990 -- 1992; UA195.005.005.00021 (Box 5)
  - Community Health, 1997 -- 2004; UA195.005.005.00022 (Box 5)
  - Drama & Dance, 1996 -- 2004; UA195.005.005.00023 (Box 5)
  - Economics, 1996 -- 2004; UA195.005.005.00024 (Box 5)
  - Education, 1996 -- 2006; UA195.005.005.00025 (Box 5)
  - English, 2000 -- 2005; UA195.005.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - Geology, 1999 -- 2004; UA195.005.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - GRALL, 1999 -- 2006; UA195.005.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - History [Folder 1 of 2], 2001 -- 2006; UA195.005.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - History [Folder 2 of 2], 2003 -- 2006; UA195.005.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - Mathematics, 1998 -- 2005; UA195.005.006.00006 (Box 6)
  - Music [Folder 1 of 2], 1999 -- 2003; UA195.005.006.00007 (Box 6)
  - Music [Folder 2 of 2], 1998 -- 2005; UA195.005.006.00008 (Box 6)
  - Occupational Therapy, 2002 -- 2006; UA195.005.006.00009 (Box 6)
  - Philosophy, 1998 -- 2005; UA195.005.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - Physics & Astronomy [Folder 1 of 2], 1998 -- 2004; UA195.005.006.00011 (Box 6)
  - Physics & Astronomy [Folder 2 of 2], 1999 -- 2005; UA195.005.006.00012 (Box 6)
  - Political Science, 1998 -- 2005; UA195.005.006.00013 (Box 6)
  - Psychology, 1998 -- 2005; UA195.005.006.00014 (Box 6)
  - Religion, 1995 -- 2002; UA195.005.006.00015 (Box 6)
  - Romance Languages [Folder 1 of 2], 1999 -- 2002; UA195.005.006.00016 (Box 6)
  - Romance Languages [Folder 2 of 2], 2000 -- 2005; UA195.005.006.00017 (Box 6)
  - Sociology/Anthropology, 1998 -- 2004; UA195.005.006.00018 (Box 6)
  - UEP, 2002 -- 2004; UA195.005.007.00001 (Box 7)
  - Visual and Critical Studies, 1998 -- 2004; UA195.005.007.00002 (Box 7)
  - Anthropology, 2003 -- 2008; UA195.005.007.00003 (Box 7)
  - Art/Art History Faculty Info Sheets, 2003 -- 2008; UA195.005.007.00004 (Box 7)
  - Biology, 2003 -- 2008; UA195.005.007.00005 (Box 7)
  - Chemistry Faculty Info Sheets, 2003 -- 2008; UA195.005.007.00006 (Box 7)
  - Classics Faculty Info Sheets, 2003 -- 2008; UA195.005.007.00007 (Box 7)
  - Child Development, 2003 -- 2008; UA195.005.007.00008 (Box 7)
  - Community Health, 2003 -- 2008; UA195.005.007.00009 (Box 7)
  - Drama & Dance, 2003 -- 2008; UA195.005.007.00010 (Box 7)
  - Economics B-K Faculty Info Sheets, 2003 -- 2008; UA195.005.007.00011 (Box 7)
  - Economics M-S Faculty Info Sheets, 2003 -- 2008; UA195.005.007.00012 (Box 7)
  - English Faculty Info Sheets, 2003 -- 2008; UA195.005.007.00013 (Box 7)
  - Education, 2003 -- 2008; UA195.005.007.00014 (Box 7)
  - Geology, 2003 -- 2008; UA195.005.007.00015 (Box 7)
  - GRALL, 2003 -- 2008; UA195.005.007.00016 (Box 7)
  - History, 2003 -- 2008; UA195.005.007.00017 (Box 7)
  - Math, 2003 -- 2008; UA195.005.007.00018 (Box 7)
  - Music, 2003 -- 2008; UA195.005.007.00019 (Box 7)
  - Physics & Astronomy Faculty Info Sheets, 2003 -- 2008; UA195.005.016.00001 (Box 16)
  - Psychology Faculty Info Sheets, 2003 -- 2008; UA195.005.016.00002 (Box 16)
  - Philosophy, 2003 -- 2008; UA195.005.016.00003 (Box 16)
  - Political Science, 2003 -- 2008; UA195.005.016.00004 (Box 16)
  - OT Faculty Info Sheets, 2003 -- 2008; UA195.005.016.00005 (Box 16)
  - Religion, 2003 -- 2008; UA195.005.016.00006 (Box 16)
  - Romance Languages, 2003 -- 2008; UA195.005.016.00007 (Box 16)
  - Sociology Faculty Info Sheets, 2003 -- 2008; UA195.005.016.00008 (Box 16)
  - UEP, 2003 -- 2008; UA195.005.016.00009 (Box 16)
  - Visual & Critical Studies, 2003 -- 2008; UA195.005.016.00010 (Box 16)
- Subject Files, 2001 -- 2009; UA195.006; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series consists of subject files related to special projects.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by accession.
  - Academic Leadership Program 2008, UA195.006.012.00001 (Box 12)
  - Admissions, 2005 -- 2006; UA195.006.012.00002 (Box 12)
  - Admissions/Enrollment Management, 2002 -- 2004; UA195.006.012.00003 (Box 12)
  - Alumni House Legal Issue - May 2007, UA195.006.012.00004 (Box 12)
  - AAUP, 2007; UA195.006.012.00005 (Box 12)
  - Audit Reports, 2003 -- 2008; UA195.006.012.00006 (Box 12)
  - Audit & Mgmt Advisory Svcs, 2005 -- 2009; UA195.006.012.00007 (Box 12)
  - Block Schedule, 2005; UA195.006.012.00008 (Box 12)
  - Dean's Feedback, 2001 -- 2002; UA195.006.012.00009 (Box 12)
  - Disability Services, 2004; UA195.006.012.00010 (Box 12)
  - Drinking, 2001 -- 2002; UA195.006.012.00011 (Box 12)
  - Faculty Size, 2005; UA195.006.012.00012 (Box 12)
  - Financial Aid, 2003; UA195.006.012.00013 (Box 12)
  - HR Org Dev & Training A&S, 2008; UA195.006.012.00014 (Box 12)
  - Information Technology (IT), 2003 -- 2004; UA195.006.012.00015 (Box 12)
  - Institutional Research, 2002 -- 2007; UA195.006.012.00016 (Box 12)
  - Proposal for Interdisciplinary Studies, 2008; UA195.006.012.00017 (Box 12)
  - New Hires, 2008 -- 2009; UA195.006.012.00018 (Box 12)
  - Nutter McClennen & Fish Attorneys at Law, 2005; UA195.006.012.00019 (Box 12)
  - Naked Quad Run, 2002; UA195.006.012.00020 (Box 12)
  - Open CourseWare Initiative (Sept. '05), 2005 -- 2009; UA195.006.012.00021 (Box 12)
  - Outside Legal Fees for A&S, 2004 -- 2009; UA195.006.012.00022 (Box 12)
  - Post Docs, 2005; UA195.006.012.00023 (Box 12)
  - Power Failure, 2007; UA195.006.012.00024 (Box 12)
  - Professor of the Practice, 2007; UA195.006.012.00025 (Box 12)
  - R.E.A.L Program, 2005; UA195.006.012.00026 (Box 12)
  - Safety Issues, 2002 -- 2004; UA195.006.012.00027 (Box 12)
  - Student Services, 2005; UA195.006.012.00028 (Box 12)
  - TEMS, 2005; UA195.006.012.00029 (Box 12)
  - TCU Senate [1 of 2], 2002 -- 2003; UA195.006.012.00030 (Box 12)
  - TCU Senate [2 of 2], 2002 -- 2003; UA195.006.012.00031 (Box 12)
  - Tulane (Fall), 2005; UA195.006.012.00032 (Box 12)
  - Turnitin Plagiarism Prevention Program, 2006; UA195.006.012.00033 (Box 12)
  - University Counsel, 2005; UA195.006.012.00034 (Box 12)
  - V.P. for Student Services, 2002; UA195.006.012.00035 (Box 12)
- Meeting Minutes, 1988 -- 2010; UA195.007; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series contains records of faculty, committee, and executive committee meetings.
  This series is arranged chronologically by accession.
  - AS&E Minutes [1 of 4], 2004 -- 2005; UA195.007.013.00001 (Box 13)
  - AS&E Minutes [2 of 4], 2004 -- 2005; UA195.007.013.00002 (Box 13)
  - AS&E Minutes [3 of 4], 2004 -- 2005; UA195.007.013.00003 (Box 13)
  - AS&E Minutes [4 of 4], 2004 -- 2005; UA195.007.013.00004 (Box 13)
  - AS&E Minutes, 2005 -- 2006; UA195.007.013.00005 (Box 13)
  - A & S Department Chairs and Program Directors meetings, 2006 -- 2007; UA195.007.013.00006 (Box 13)
  - A & S Department Chairs and Program Directors Meetings, 2007 -- 2008; UA195.007.013.00007 (Box 13)
  - Budget & University Priorities Committee, 1997 -- 2006; UA195.007.013.00008 (Box 13)
  - Curricula Committee (LA&J), 2010; UA195.007.013.00009 (Box 13)
  - Culture Option, 2005 -- 2006; UA195.007.013.00010 (Box 13)
  - Educational Policy Committee, 1999 -- 2000; UA195.007.013.00011 (Box 13)
  - Outcomes Assessment Committee [1 of 3], 2007 -- 2010; UA195.007.013.00012 (Box 13)
  - Outcomes Assessment Committee [2 of 3], 2007 -- 2010; UA195.007.013.00013 (Box 13)
  - Outcomes Assessment Committee [3 of 3], 2007 -- 2010; UA195.007.013.00014 (Box 13)
  - Faculty Research Report & Facilities Advisory Committee, 1988 -- 2003; UA195.007.013.00015 (Box 13)
  - Chair's Handbook, 1904 -- 1989; UA195.007.013.00016 (Box 13)
  - Faculty Handbook Research, 2002 -- 2003; UA195.007.013.00017 (Box 13)
  - Arts and Sciences Faculty Handbook, 1995; UA195.007.013.00018 (Box 13)
- Orientation, 1996 -- 2006; UA195.008; 2.4 Linear Feet
  This series contains records of New Faculty and New Chair orientation sessions.
  This series is arranged chronologically within New Faculty and New Chair orientation sessions.
  - New Faculty Orientation, 1996 -- 1997; UA195.008.014.00001 (Box 14)
  - New Faculty Orientation, 1998 -- 1999; UA195.008.014.00002 (Box 14)
  - New Faculty Orientation, 1999 -- 2000; UA195.008.014.00003 (Box 14)
  - New Faculty Orientation, 1999 -- 2000; UA195.008.014.00004 (Box 14)
  - New Faculty Orientation, 2001 -- 2002; UA195.008.014.00005 (Box 14)
  - New Faculty Orientation, 2001 -- 2002; UA195.008.014.00006 (Box 14)
  - New Faculty Orientation, 2001 -- 2002; UA195.008.014.00007 (Box 14)
  - New Faculty Orientation, 2003 -- 2004; UA195.008.014.00008 (Box 14)
  - New Faculty Orientation, 2003 -- 2004; UA195.008.014.00009 (Box 14)
  - New Faculty Orientation, 2003 -- 2004; UA195.008.014.00010 (Box 14)
  - New Faculty Orientation, 2004 -- 2005; UA195.008.014.00011 (Box 14)
  - New Faculty Orientation, 2004 -- 2005; UA195.008.014.00012 (Box 14)
  - New Faculty Orientation, 2005 -- 2006; UA195.008.014.00013 (Box 14)
  - New Faculty Orientation, 2005 -- 2006; UA195.008.014.00014 (Box 14)
  - New Faculty Orientation Packet, 2005 -- 2006; UA195.008.014.00015 (Box 14)
  - Interview Phase 1, 2005 -- 2006; UA195.008.014.00016 (Box 14)
  - New Faculty Orientation Thank Yous, 2005 -- 2006; UA195.008.014.00017 (Box 14)
  - New Chairs Orientation [1 of 5], 1999 -- 2003; UA195.008.015.00001 (Box UA195 Shared 4)
  - New Chairs Orientation [2 of 5], 1999 -- 2003; UA195.008.015.00002 (Box UA195 Shared 4)
  - New Chair Orientation [3 of 5], 1999 -- 2003; UA195.008.015.00003 (Box UA195 Shared 4)
  - New Chair Orientation [4 of 5], 1999 -- 2003; UA195.008.015.00004 (Box UA195 Shared 4)
  - New Chair Orientation [5 of 5], 1999 -- 2003; UA195.008.015.00005 (Box UA195 Shared 4)
- Faculty Forum and Events, 1999 -- 2008; UA195.009; 1.2 Linear Feet; 3 Digital Object(s); 1.2 Gigabytes
  This series contains logistics and notes for Dean's Faculty Forum and other annual parties and events, and videos from two events: Constitution Day 2009 and Constitution Day 2010.
  This series is arranged chronologically by annual event.
  This series contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.
  - Book Party - Dean's Annual, 2006 -- 2008; UA195.009.015.00006 (Box UA195 Shared 4)
  - DFF, 2006; UA195.009.015.00007 (Box UA195 Shared 4)
  - Dean's Forum, 2005 -- 2006; UA195.009.015.00008 (Box UA195 Shared 4)
  - Dean's Faculty Forum, 2007 -- 2008; UA195.009.015.00009 (Box UA195 Shared 4)
  - Dennett Faculty Forum, 2006; UA195.009.015.00010 (Box UA195 Shared 4)
  - Peter Der Manuelian, 2006; UA195.009.015.00011 (Box UA195 Shared 4)
  - Dean's Faculty Forum, 2005 -- 2006; UA195.009.015.00012 (Box UA195 Shared 4)
  - Holiday Party, 1999 -- 2005; UA195.009.015.00013 (Box UA195 Shared 4)
  - Constitution Day, 2009; UA195.009.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 623 Megabytes
    Video recording of Constitution Day event at Tufts in 2009, with guest speaker David King.
  - Constitution Day, 2010; UA195.009.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 235 Megabytes
    Video recording of Constitution Day event at Tufts in 2010.
  - Constitution Day 2011, 2011-September-16; UA195.000419; 1 Digital Object(s); 354.19 Megabytes
    Video recording of Constitution Day event at Tufts in 2011.
- Additional accessions, 1994 -- 2011; UA195.010; 1.2 Linear Feet
  - Invitation, College of Liberal Arts and Jackson College, 1994; UA195-001 (Box 1)